Ever
wonders to get the guaranteed returns for your
whole life if you get old and in case of
any miss happening to you your spouse will get that
guaranteed income for her and his whole life
yes there is a plan for it I am going to reveal this
secret today just set listen
carefully for next 10 minutes good
morning everyone this is mayaan kharbanda and
let's talk about ICC Prudential
Additional Pension Plan GPP Flexi
Guaranteed Pension Plan Flexi which is the
best and unique in its nature and beats
all the competitors plans pension plans and
their returns normally what do the competitors do competitors
compare it with FD and rental income but can
ICC Prudential Guaranteed Pension Plan
Flexi be compared with FD and rental income
absolute no because
its returns are much much better than FD and
rental income how FD gives you what
interest rates  As of today, it is at 6,
at 7, if some banks or corporates have
invested their money then it is at 8, but were these interest
rates the same even 30 years ago?
No, they were approximately at around 16
in 1989. Every 10 years, it is at 3. Interest
rates fall, RBI reduces them, why does it
reduce them? Because inflation comes down, the
economy improves, repo rates
are decreased so that loans become cheaper, people can
take loans, expand their businesses,
buy houses. So, repo rates have to come down,
FD rates have to decrease. Will it
remain at 78 even after 5 years? No, if you remember,
in 2019, it had come down to 6, due to Corona, they had to increase, that is why
inflation is big, but will it remain at 78 after 5 years?
No, it will remain there
because the economy has to grow, the
ongoing global tensions will also reduce
and as soon as these reduce, inflation will also increase.  It will
decrease and as inflation decreases RBI will
reduce FD rates but ICICI
Prudential Guaranteed Plan Flexi offers
you the best interest rate from 7.5 to 14 percent
guaranteed simple interest right from the
first day you take the policy and it goes till
you are alive resting rental incomes rental
incomes in India do not give more than 3 to 4 percent
return on top of that
how many cells are there in rental incomes how is the tenant does the
tenant pay on time or not
property maintenance has to be done sometimes
tenant is available sometimes the property is
lying vacant but there is no tension here
return of 7 to 14 percent right from the first day that is
guaranteed if corona comes the tenant's work may
or may not run he may lose his job no tension any
problems may come in the world economy
but this income will keep coming to you guaranteed
what would you like to understand this plan
in detail let us understand the features and
benefits of GPP Flexi who can take
this product the person who  Key Age is above 40 years
and below 70 years The age has to be between
40 to 70 years Those people can only take
this plan Nt Options There are two
kinds of options in this plan Single
Life and Joint Life In Joint Life, the second
holder has to have age more than 30 years
Return of premium is one of the best
option in this plan Waiver of premium in
Joint Life scenario is a mesmerizing
feature Income returns in this plan Age I
Explain Early are better than FD and
rental incomes if we put all the features
together Premium paying term and deferment
period play the most important role in
this plan to get the best returns possible Let's see two
illustrations as an example
to understand the basics Single Life with
Return of Premium and Joint Life with
Return of Premium In Single Life, the age is
50 years Premium paying term is 8
years  If the deferment period is 10 years,
then from the 11th year onwards, he will start getting money
and the premium he is paying yearly
is 10 lakhs. From the 11th year onwards, the person
will get 737, 537
and in case of unfortunate, he will get
80 lakhs. You can see that
8 years are given in the illustration. From the 11th year,
73000 starts coming. We can understand this in detail on a
case to case basis. Now comes to joint
life. The premium paying term is 8
years and the deferment is 10 years, so
he gives 5 lakhs for 8 years. From the 11th year onwards, he
starts getting 9353 and this life long will happen
that as soon as the first holder
dies and he does not survive, if
any mishappening happens to him, then your
amount is NT payments, that
starts coming to the second holder and as soon as
any mishappening happens to the second holder,
he does not survive.  Yes, the entire
money which you have given ₹ 5 lakh * 8 years, the
nominee gets all that money.
These are the very basic illustrations
set as an example. Returns will differ
from case to case basis. Major returns depend
upon the premium paying terms
and the deferment period which I
explain. Also, if any doubts or
clarification required do message or call us
on the given numbers. Thank you very
much.